<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0">

<channel>
  <title>Melodity - DIY Musician Blog</title>
  <link>https://www.melodity.com</link>
  <description>Want to learn how to get paid gigs, write original songs, and make professional recordings at home yourself? Melodity has all the expert tips and tricks you need to become a DIY Musician.</description>
  
  <item>
    <title>About Us - Melodity</title>
    <link>https://www.melodity.com/about.html</link>
    <description>Melodity is a daily updated DIY Musician blog for musicians of all levels. We provide how-to's, tips, and tricks from real-life experts...</description>
  </item>

  <item>
    <title>Catagories - Melodity</title>
    <link>https://www.melodity.com/catagories.html</link>
    <description>Melodity provides a variety of topics on writing original songs, creating instrumentals in GarageBand, getting paid gigs, real-life stories, and other...</description>
  </item>

  <item>
    <title>Contact Us - Melodity</title>
    <link>https://www.melodity.com/contact.html</link>
    <description>Want to sponsor us? Is there content you want to see? Do you have ideas or suggestions? Contact us now! Melodity has all the expert tips and tricks you need to become a DIY Musician.</description>
  </item>

  <item>
    <title>Privacy Policy, Terms and Conditions, Disclaimer - Melodity</title>
    <link>https://www.melodity.com/privacypolicy.html</link>
    <description>Melodity privacy policy, terms and conditions, and diclaimer. By using Melodity.com, you consent to...</description>
  </item>

  <item>
    <title>Store - Melodity</title>
    <link>https://www.melodity.com/store.html</link>
    <description>Expert ebooks on how to get paid gigs without an agent, How to make your own presskit and take professional photos at home, DIY Musician how-to guides...</description>
  </item>

  <item>
    <title>How to Find Your Unique Edge - Melodity</title>
    <link>https://www.melodity.com/find-your-unique-edge.html</link>
    <description>Do your covers sound like every other musician? Does it feel like something is just missing, like the spark in your cover isn’t lighting up? Maybe it’s time to try and find your unique edge.
    This guide is going to show you how to experiment with different genres and styles of music/singing to find your sweet spot, then incorporate them into your songs.</description>
  </item>
  
  <item>
    <title>How to Find Local Open Mics - Melodity</title>
    <link>https://www.melodity.com/how-to-find-open-mics.html</link>
    <description>It is not easy to get up in front of a crowd and sing, but this how-to guide is going to provide you with everything you need to help you be a success. From finding the right type of open mic for your genre and skill level to giving you all the pro tips you might not have thought of. After all, no one wants to be a little teen popstar singing a love song in a biker bar.</description>
  </item>
  
  <item>
    <title>Networking for Introverts - Melodity</title>
    <link>https://www.melodity.com/networking-for-introverts.html</link>
    <description>If you’re like me and utterly hate talking to people, then I bet you are already cringing from this article. But fear not my fellow turtles! This article has all the tricks for networking, without actually having to network!</description>
  </item>

  <item>
    <title>Why You Need a Fanbase - Melodity</title>
    <link>https://www.melodity.com/why-you-need-a-fanbase.html</link>
    <description>A fanbase is one of the most important tools any musician can have. Fans not only support your music, buy your merchandise, and come to your shows, but they can also give you a community. Having a loyal fanbase will help you make money, get bigger gigs, and help you get even more fans.</description>
  </item>

  <item>
    <title>6 Free Resources To Build Your Fanbase - Melodity</title>
    <link>https://www.melodity.com/6-free-resources-to-build-your-fanbase.html</link>
    <description>Having an online presence is important for every musician, it allows your fans to connect with you, engage with your content, and keep them up to date with everything new. To get started, below are the basic resources every musician should consider having. We will discuss each of their unique benefits and disadvantages below.</description>
  </item>
  


</channel>

</rss>
